Visit turkision.com for more!
Alps.
Brother.
Allah is the greatest!
Alps! Strike your swords, for union!
For being hope to the oppressed!
Allah is the greatest!
You will vomit blood, find death!
Strip their flesh
Alaeddin!
Alps have become martyr. May tyrants meet hell.
My Allah, help me.
Come on Alps, come on.
Ya Allah!
The lust of death bringing
spirits is on our swords!
All of you will taste this curse!
Commander, some of them are catching up.
They will only find death when they arrive.
My soldiers, we've done what
we could. Now we fall back!
Come on, come on.
Why are mongols falling back?
I do not know master.
-Boran, check the wounded.
-Okay my bey.
My bey, my bey.
Orhan. Orhan.
Are you alright? Come on, get up.
-Come on, get up.
-Son.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Sultan.
Help me, take him.
Get up my son.
-We lost a lot, my bey.
-Alps, alps..
Alaeddin! Alps, bring water!
Come, come. Give me this water.
What is this. What is this..
You will be alright.
Mehmed. My son.
-Mehmed?
-Father.
-Mehmed.
-Are you alright, my son?
-Father.
-Brother.
-My brother, you are alright.
Gurbuz.
Alps.
"Indeed, to Allah we belong
and to Allah we shall return."
-What happened, my son?
-They've come unexpected.
They stroke us, then retreated into the woods.
What are you standing for? After them!
Yakup Bey.
Yakup Bey! They blatantly
ambushed, they must've thought after.
Think about that and act accordingly.
The blood of alps is on your hands.
Pull yourself together, Osman Bey.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Am I allowed, Malhun Hatun?
I've said what I've said, my daughter.
I know, however please listen to me.
Do not disappoint me, Aysima.
You lied about Holofira.
There is no explanation.
Malhun Hatun. When someone..
Falls in love..
They do things that they
never thought of doing.
If you never came to me, I wouldn't even
dreamed about being a hatun for Orhan Bey.
However, you've been such a mother
to me, you've given me such hope..
I got scared that Holofira will destroy this.
You are right, my daughter.
However, you did not let Holofira
destroy it. You did it all by yourself.
There is no excuse for
what I've done. I know that.
However, please forgive me.
Or I will never forgive myself.
You have to apologize to Holofira before me.
I am not the one to decide what
happens next, Orhan Bey will decide.
How will you pay for what you've done?
Don't talk like you've never got
ambushed before, Osman Bey.
We know your past as well.
We've never experienced such a disaster before.
What are you saying, Yakup
Bey? You will pay for all of this here.
You will take care of the families
of these alps for the rest of your life.
Who are you to command me?
-Know your place.
-Who are you?
Osman Bey, we have martyrs.
Don't do this, for
them at least.
Tell me. Who gave you this idea?
Who?
Who told you to strike during the trade? Who?
It is my fault.
With my merchant mind I couldn't have known.
Vasilis or Veysel, whatever he
is called. He is quite important..
Quite valuable to the crusaders.
I heard that, and I told my
Yakup Bey. I shouldn't have.
My Sultan has decided a trade. However..
They wanted to strike them while
trading, that is fit for my Sultan.
With this infidel, trade is only possible..
With sword anyways. He did what
fit him. However, it didn't go well.
My Osman Bey. I know there
are a lot of traitors among us.
However, may Allah be my
judge, I am not a traitor. If I am..
May Allah not allow me to leave these woods.
If there is one to blame, that is me.
If there is a head to take
...it's mine.
I assume full responsibility, Osman Bey.
Ayhan Agha...
Ayhan Agha.
I thought you were a skillful
merchant who loves his nation.
I am..
Thank you, my Bey.
I owe you two lives.
Don't worry. Nobody will remain indebted to me.
It's your turn, beys. You should know
this. Neither loyalty nor sultanate matters!
There is only fight! I'm going to fight now.
Anyone can join me.
Even if you don't join me
and if the enemy show mercy,
...I will take no offense, anyway.
Alps.
Take the martyrs and the wounded.
We, as beys, will discuss the matter.
Things are happening too fast, Yakup Bey.
May your journey be safe and your minds sharp.
Don't be agitated.
Think thoroughly.
Go ahead. Stay safe.
Where are you going, Ayhan Agha?
Alps, we had been suspecting.
And our suspicion turned to be true.
-Bayindir Bey. Sons.
-My Bey.
You will go after Ayhan Agha.
My Bey, will we go after him
only because of this incident?
He caused many warriors to die!
What more can he even do, Boran Bey?
Bayindir Bey, speak.
When I followed Ayhan that day,
he led me where he kept the gold.
He looked worried about his gold.
But I know that fear well, my Bey.
There was something up. Something tricky.
That's why he used to
get lost in the battlefield.
My Bey, do you think Ayhan set up this game?
Let’s not hurry to judge, brother.
We all heard. He's a tradesman.
He's afraid of war. He was looking for a
place to hide when our Bey saved him.
Sons, there may be a coincidence.
If justice is broken once,
...both the state and the
nation won't get better anymore.
For this reason, we'll be sure first.
Then the heads will fall on the ground.
Nobody will act without
orders before we are sure.
-Okay, my Bey.
-Bayindir Bey.
Sons. Get back to your duties now.
We'll spread around and
learn everything about Ayhan.
Let's go!
Osman spared your life but I
haven't interrogated you yet.
My Sultan.
The battle has just begun. I am exhausted.
We should go and cure our wounds.
May your merchandise be cursed!
You smell the gold from a hundred miles away.
But you don't realize you are
being drawn into a trap, huh?
Or you realized.
And they paid you well in return
for drawing us into the trap, ha?
Oh, my Sultan... No way.
Would I betray my nation
while we have so many martyrs?
Look. I'm not like Osman.
I would break your neck.
You let that dog run off. My alps
got slaughtered because of you.
Leave him, Mehmed. Let him speak.
Mehmed Bey.
My Sultan, I'm only
good at trade. That's right.
But it doesn't mean I'm a treacherous man.
I don't need to get rich with treachery at all.
Thanks to Allah, I've earned enough so far.
May Allah be my witness. I said
just some words and look at this.
-I'd gladly lose money instead of my life!
-Ayhan Agha.
Go away. And stay out of my sight for a while.
Go!
As Mighty Sultan orders.
I will be away...
...until I deserve your forgiveness.
Mehmed Bey.
I'm already invisible, fools.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Sultan.
Send a man after him I want
to know every move of his.
As you order, my Sultan.
What are your orders for us, my Bey?
A Bey wouldn't order anything but fight.
For the blood of Gurbuz and the other martyrs,
...we will fight.
Now, give the swords we took
from the caravan to our people.
Take the rest to the Beys.
Yes my Bey.
The Alps will take courage
after they see the swords.
My Bey. You never give swords
before showing us the target.
Tell us, where will we walk?
We will walk to Kite.
Prepare the army and the
things we need for a siege.
Yes my Bey.
The swords will make Alps happy,
and the news of a gaza (Islamic war)..
...will make everyone gather behind us.
Mongols were going to think we
were scared after the last incident.
They will see that they were
wrong after our conquest.
We will show them that we are not scared now...
...not before the conquest.
My Bey... The archers positioned
themselves within ambush range.
Our children are after the traitor
our Hodjas are after the cruel.
Cerkutay! Like old times, huh?
Okay my Bey. The revenge of Alps...
...and Gurbuz brother
will be taken if Allah permits.
-For sure!
-My Bey...
Shooting the Governor of
Konya is shooting Olcaytu.
We are not afraid. But it will cost us a lot.
We have to shoot that dog
before we arrive in Konya.
Or else, or else... We
will be in great trouble.
Alps! Today, the end of the cruel will come.
Come on!
We killed his Alps. His
Shahzades were going to die.
We had enough power to
kill them all. We were so close.
Send news to Osman Bey.
Those who cannot rule power
are crushed under that power.
Those who know when to put their
swords back in their sheathes always win.
Osman and Yakup saw our strength.
Soon, they will lose their heads, huh?
We will go right away and unite with Horsemen.
If one's horse dies, he will go on foot, if
one's courage dies, he will lose his life.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Are you feeling better,
my beautiful daughter?
Thank you.
Sure, I am alright.
There is nothing to feel sorry for.
Those who are right always stand tall.
That's what I expected from you.
And people who blamed
you before listening to you..
...saw your nobleness in the marketplace.
Holofira..
-Are you busy?
I am not going to listen to
you while you insult me, Aysima.
Leave my counter, or else...
You are right about everything. I
came here to ask for forgiveness.
Forgiveness?
Everyone was talking
about us in the marketplace.
They said "Holofira took your fiance
from you, and you are just watching them."
When I heard it, I lost my mind.
But I know that you are not guilty. Besides,
you were not the one who promised me.
I did wrong. Forgive me.
Good.
Still, do not come across me again.
Aysima seems genuine, but...
...still, I cannot be
relieved before I test her.
Asking for forgiveness requires bravery.
She made us suspicious
for once. It would be
beneficial to investigate
thoroughly, you are right.
Let's see. If Holofira accepts being a
Muslim, then everything will change.
Each age of children is a different test.
I hope we can help them get married happily.
Aameen Bala. Aameen.
Did you do something about
Gonca? Did something new happen?
Sure. Sure. Alaeddin told Gonca he loved her.
I think Gonca loves him too.
-May it be blessed.
Being co-in-laws with Yakup
Bey is going to be hard, I know.
But... Gonca is a noble
girl. She is a good person.
Right, Ulgen? What do you think?
You stayed with them for a long time.
Would Gonca be a good daughter-in-law?
I... I don't know.
Gonca Hatun! Gonca Hatun!
Gonca Hatun!
Ghazi Alp. What happened?
Why are you in a rush?
What can happen? Someone wants to
see you again. They said it's important.
-Who invited me?
-Alaeddin Bey.
But... you cannot go anywhere
without me anymore. I'll come with you.
Not today, Ghazi Alp. Besides, look what
I brought for you. Let me give it to you.
This is for you.
But...
She is gone.
-Do you also have something for me?
-No, VAIIah, my Shahzade.
I lost Gonca Hatun because
of these. These are all mine!
Good. Go and enjoy then.
Why did you come, Orhan?
Everyone is watching us. Don't you see?
You know that I am waiting for your answer.
I gave you an answer. I won't become Muslim.
Holofira...
What do you think is not reasonable? Ask me.
Ask me, I will tell you about our religion.
I know you need time. But..
Do not reject my offer
without thinking about it. Look...
I am saying that if you become
Muslim, we will get married.
This is my mother's only condition.
Why am I the one who has
to sacrifice something, Orhan?
I will not be a Muslim.
Look at me, I will never be a Muslim.
Don't do this.
Think about it.
There's nothing to think about.
I've said what I have to say.
I'm listening to you, Gonca.
Are you playing hard to get again?
No. I'm not playing hard to get.
Then answer me. Coy woman.
I'm thinking about how
am I going to tell you this.
Alaeddin Bey.
You misunderstood me.
If you think I have feelings
for you, you're wrong.
What are you saying, Gonca?
You've heard me.
I don't love you.
-Don't get in my way anymore.
-Trickster woman.
-What are you doing?
-What does that mean, Gonca?
-You've heard me.
-Move away.
-No.
No, I don't get it.
What has changed since yesterday?
-Alaeddin, move away.
-Gonca.
You asked me that
"do you trust me?"
I trust you.
I trust you as much as I trust myself.
But don't expect me to believe these words.
Believe it or not.
Go away now.
Gonca. Gonca, what is the reason?
Is it my family? Is it my mother?
Tell me something, Gonca.
Alaeddin, move.
Gonca.
Then look me in the eye and tell me.
Don't you love me?
Alaeddin, don't force it.
Don't get in my way again.
Come on.
Gonca!
I don't believe what your
tongue says, I believe your eyes.
-Come on!
-I believe your eyes.
Your eyes.
I got my answer.
-Alaeddin.
-Brother.
Look at me.
What happened to you
-Gonca doesn't love me, brother.
-What are you saying, Alaeddin?
Brother. When I heard that
my heart ached so much...
...I thought I'd never breathe again.
I wouldn't be able to breathe if her
eyes weren't saying something different.
Eyes tell the truth, brother.
We will not hear the words.
What about you? What did you do?
Did Holofira accept being a Muslim?
She didn't. It seems she won't accept it.
I'm stuck between my mother and Holofira.
What are we going to do, brother?
We will do our best. We will work hard.
We will do our duty first.
Think of it this way.
I'm also dealing with Mehmed,
but your only opponent is Ghazi.
Don't say that. Ghazi is
a tough opponent as well.
All right, let’s see your
skills as well. Come on.
Come on.
Alps! Shoot the glorious arrows of Kayi!
Allah is the Greatest.
Nokers! Defend!
Karecelasun, or whatever you are
where are you going without dying?
I did not die even in epic battles.
Do you think I'd die in your hands, Osman?
You will. Whoever comes
these lands and sheds blood
will be buried in these lands. Alps!
-Attack!
-Release the horses!
Gonca. Are you all right?
-I'm all right.
-Come.
-What happened?
-I'm in such a trouble that
-I can't even breathe now.
-All right.
All right, come. Come, have a seat.
What happened, tell me?
Do you remember what I told you about Alaeddin?
Let's keep it as a secret, all right?
All right. I'll not tell anyone about it.
But tell me, what bothers you so much?
You told me that it is impossible
between you and Orhan Bey.
It is impossible for us too now.
Everything is over.
But why? Because of your families?
This is not something you can't overcome.
Maybe the tension between
them will be over thanks to you.
Both my family and...
No. No, Holofira. There's
no such thing as "us".
I told Alaeddin that I don't love him.
-Everything is over.
-What did you do, Gonca?
Gonca isn't acting by her heart
anymore. You should just know this.
What about Alaaddin?
What did he say?
He didn't believe.
My Allah... I need to stay alone for a while.
Thanks for everything.
You drew Ilkhanid wrath on
you. But there won't be only this.
Your frontiers will turn
into a bloodbath, Osman.
We are not afraid of death.
We will always walk on the
right path against the wrong.
Brother, is your hand fully recovered?
Why are you carrying double swords?
You got your answer?
Yes, brother.
You should still watch your back, brother.
You call me brother.
You watch my back.
-Come on. Come on!
-Come on.
Osman... Don't take my sword!
Do not touch!
Osman!
Osman, I will take your head!
I will take your head and
be a legend here, Osman!
-Your legend would be vain! You will die!
-Come on.
Nokers, protect the commander...
Nokers.
-Draw back.
-Where are you going?
You are running off again?
Running off again? Alps!
Boran, send our best trackers after them.
Sure, my Bey. Yagiz, Dumrul, Ayaz. Come on!
Before even the blood of
Gurbuz and our martyrs dried,
...we slaughtered all the dogs, my Bey.
But we couldn't take the
head of the leading dog yet.
Don't be worrying! We'll take
revenge from the heathens.
I took that dog's sword
and will take his life too.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
Germiyanoglu Border / Border Market
Orhan doesn't care about you,
Holofira. He only cares about himself.
Why would you sacrifice?
He doesn't know how important
what he wants me to do is to me.
What does he even do? Look
what he has done to Aysima.
I'm sorry about that girl.
-After what she did?
-She was blinded by her anger.
I can't be angry with her.
They disgraced her. Unbelievable.
Everybody is talking about you.
Still?
Orhan's walking around you bothered people.
They said he would marry Aysima.
So people got confused.
These are not appropriate, Holofira.
It's not my fault. You know that.
Of course it's not.
Orhan does everything but you and Aysima...
...get harm.
Actually, there is something more important.
My aunt.
I didn't tell her about anything going on here.
But she realized.
She always does.
She keeps pushing me.
I don't know what to do.
I do.
I think...
...your aunt and I should meet.
What do you think?
Guice, speak. What's going on?
Gonca Hatun told Alaaddin
Bey she didn't love him.
Good. Now we have something else to do.
We'll make preparations. We're
going to meet Holofira's family tonight.
Obviously, they will ask
for Holofira for marriage.
Nobody knows that. Keep your mouth shut.
Which brother should I be upset about
now? I should go to the palace immediately.
Come on.
Whatever happens helps Osman.
He's drawing beys one by one on his side.
I will show all of them the truth.
But Cerkutay has an account to give first.
I sent him to the palace to
be my eyes and ears there.
But he became deaf an mute.
Osman grew his reputation bigger
by attacking the caravan of weapons.
-If he knew but didn't tell us...
-He will pay for it.
But we will be sure first.
There is an important matter, Yakup Bey.
-What is it, hatun?
-Something good.
Very good, actually. Holofira...
...is so confused.
-Did she say something? Did she accept?
-No.
But she knows we want to meet her aunt...
...because of what happened here.
But will we do more than just meeting.
Are you sure about your decision, Mehmed?
That's what matters.
I will do whatever my mother and father say.
Then we will handle this thing.
Make your preparations,
hatun. We will both meet...
...and take the girl.
-Did you hand out the swords?
-We handed them all out, my bey.
Those who went to beys
should've arrived by now.
Alright.
The alps there retreated to the
encampment without losing caution, my bey.
The swords will be at the encampment tomorrow.
-However, no one will know, Cerkutay.
-Okay, my bey.
Alps, the conquest of Kite is very important.
However, no one will act independently.
-Okay my bey.
-That place will fall sooner or later.
However, now it is waiting for its time.
The sons are after Ayhan.
Before those mongols reassamble..
If we find that crusader dog, not only Kite..
But we will walk to Iznik to Bursa if Allah permits
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
-If Allah permits.
We will see after the sons
come back with their hands full.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too, Aykurt.
Did we do our last duty for Gurbuz?
We did, my bey. Our brother Gurbuz..
And the other martyr alps have reached Allah.
Their graves and their bravery
will last forever, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
This mace that belonged to Gurbuz is now yours.
Preserve it as it deserves.
Okay my bey. Okay.
Those who broke our brother Gurbuz...
The heads of those who made our alps martyrs...
Will be crushed by these mace
if Allah permits.
We did not wander around as
well, brother. We scattered them.
We spilled the blood of those who spilled ours.
Thank Allah. Our martyrs
will sleep peacefully if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits.
Those who walk on the right path, only
find peace when they become martyrs.
May they rest peacefully, if Allah permits.
-Ameen.
Place the flying flames where
I told you, but be very careful.
Their eyes are on us. Clean up this place.
Ayhan Aga, open the door.
I will stall them.
Clean this place.
-Understood, master.
-Come on.
Ayhan Aga, don't think a
sherbet is too much trouble.
Be ready.
We will take lives if needed. Open the door.
Ayhan Aga, open the door.
-Peace be upon you. Ayhan Aga.
-Peace be upon you, may Allah's mercy be upon you.
My shahzade. What is it, at this hour?
What is it that brought you to my door?
-What, did we disturb you?
-Of course not, my shahzade.
Of course not. I was thinking of you.
If you sent the word, I would've
come to you, my shahzade.
-You wouldn't get tired.
-If we call you..
Of course, you will come Ayhan Aga.
However, we wanted..
To come and see you in your place.
There are complaints about you.
-There are complaints about me?
-Complaints.
I don't know who made a complaint, however..
My shahzades, my beys with alps before them..
Came all the way to my door. My shahzade..
I do not have beef with anyone.
This is how we do things, Ayhan Aga.
The son of bey comes to the smalles issue.
That is why our necks are tough.
-Tell him, Bayindir Bey.
-Ayhan Aga.
They say you take goods from
west and sell them at frontiers.
You don't even give the
tax and fiddle with prices.
Osman Bey wants to know what is up.
May Allah protect us. It is slander, a lie!
Those snake tongue devils play trickery on me!
My shahzade, may Allah protect
me. How can I ever betray to..
This mighty state, to Osman
Bey! If I betrayed even a little bit..
May Allah not allow me to get
out from this door! It is slander!
Anything can be expected
from humanity, Ayhan Aga.
Ya Allah.
Now tell me. You won't defy
Osman Bey's command, right?
Of course not. The house is yours.
-Alright.
-And you are responsible..
With what we find here, Ayhan Aga.
-Of course, my shahzade.
-Search everywhere.
Search, so that we will have no doubts.
As you command, my shahzade.
Ayhan Aga, tell me. What is behind this door?
Don't waste your breath Ayhan
Aga. I can show it to my shahzade.
Baysungur, stay with Ayhan Aga.
There are no traces here, my bey.
There were. However they took it away.
-This is flying fire.
-He smile at our face..
And play trickery behind us.
Now he will pay for it.
-You are under arrest, Ayhan.
-I did not expect us to meet this early.
However, we will meet again.
I will have your head.
You were a friend, got our
favors. Now you will face our wrath.
What a wrath it is. I will be back!
Come on! After him, quickly!
-Malhun, look at them.
-Yes?
Bala, they are beautiful.
You are preparing a dowery, however..
It is not certain for Gonca
to say yes to Alaeddin.
Ulgen, you are hiding something.
However, you are not telling us.
-No, what can I say?
-Bala is right.
If you know something,
tell us now. This is marriage.
It is important. It is not something easy.
I don't know... Being
co-in-laws with Saadet Hatun...
What can I do? They
fell in love with each other.
Right... Look at Orhan. We couldn't make
him give up no matter what we told him.
Instead of losing our children...
What if you lose your
children with this marriage?
Mother... -Yes my daughter.
What are you doing here?
They are preparing
Gonca Hatun's dowry.
You are doing this for no reason.
Gonca Hatun does not love my brother.
What are you saying Fatma?
Where is Alaeddin now?
I was looking for my brother. But
he is not here, he is doing his duty.
It was not in our destiny.
There is something else... If my Orhan
brother hears this, there will be a disaster.
What?
Tell me Fatma. What is it?
They are going to ask for
Holofira's hand for Mehmet Bey.
Fatma... Your brother must
not hear this. Don't you tell him.
Fatma! Did you hear me?
Alright mother. Alright.
Hatuns! Hatuns!
Osman Bey is coming! I wanted to inform you.
Come on. Let's take these away.
There was a secret passage in the house,
my Bey. The dog who we thought was Ayhan...
...was even prepared for this day.
Right, my son. Right. Those men plan
their escape before they plan their moves.
Tell me. What else did
you see in Ayhan's house?
When we checked the room
behind the secret passage...
...we found the tracks of flying flame, my Bey.
Apparently, they took flying
flames out while wasting our time.
Since he put his life at
risk for the flying flame...
...he must be after a big move, my Bey.
Who knows where and how they plan to hurt us?
He came and joined our table. He made us
believe that he was Ayhan Agha. Dastard dog.
Still, we will be more careful. We cannot
let what happened in Sogut happen again.
Right. But now, we know him.
He has no where to escape.
We will cut his head off.
Tell me. War preparations
continue secretly, right?
-Right, my Bey. As you ordered.
-Thank you, thank you.
Now... Announce it to everyone...
...announce it, so that dog can also hear it.
-Yes my Bey.
-What is your goal, my Bey?
The jackal will think that the wolf's cave
is empty. He will, so he can feel our teeth.
What about Karacelasun dog?
He was assigned to Konya as a
Governor. He is working with crusaders.
Karacelasun cannot do
anything to us for some time.
We ruined him.
-Father!
-My Fatma!
My beautiful daughter...
This is that dog's sword. Did you kill him?
No... Not yet. But soon, it will happen.
Come here. Alps... Go back to your duties.
-Okay my Bey.
-So, my daughter?
Prepare a good table for us.
-Yes my Bey.
-Go now. Go.
Ayhan Agha passed away...
He was a talented trader.
Now they will face Master Gera.
From now on, we will not
hide. With all our strength...
..we will attack them.
Finally! Finally, we are
getting into a real war.
We are, Vasilis.
What are you planning
Both Germiyan and Kayi want
Holofira to be their daughter-in-law.
Is that right?
You waited all this time
until you told me this, Andra.
Didn't I tell you to...
...inform me about every step Holofira takes?
-My Hanim... I...
-Shut up!
Don't say another word!
Those immoral Turks went too far.
But I know what to do to them.
Holofira..
Is everything ready for our guests?
Yes, aunt.
Andra? Are you alright?
Andra is alright.
Go. Help them get ready.
Why is Yakup Bey coming, Holofira?
I don't know aunt. I am also curious.
Saadet Hatun... I guess she wants to meet you.
Maybe this is the best for Orhan
and Holofira. What can we do?
I think Holofira will not accept this.
I don't understand... I don't
understand why Saadet asks for Holofira.
I know what her problem is, but
she won't be able to achieve her goals.
Mother... When my brother learns
that Mehmet Bey asked for Holofira...
Don't! Don't you dare, Fatma.
Your brother will not hear about this.
What am I not supposed to hear?
Huh?
Fatma?
My sister...
Come on, tell me. Do not make me repeat.
Mehmet Bey went to
ask for Holofira's hand.
Fatma!
What?
Are you telling that to me now, my sister?
I... know what to do to Mehmet.
-The girl I love...
-Did the girl you love...
...accepted becoming a Muslim, Orhan Bey?
Mother... This is not the right time. Don't.
Orhan! This is the right time!
Did Holofira accept becoming a Muslim?
She did not! She said she
would never become a Muslim!
Was this the answer you expected?
Are you pleased now? Was this
the thing you asked for, mother?
-I just wanted you...
-Right!
You wanted me to be happy, right?
Look... Do I look happy now?
Then... we will abduct
her, my Shahzade!
Ghazi!
What is happening here?
Malhun? Orhan?
Who is abducting whom? Tell me.
Yakup Bey... He went to ask
for Holofira's hand, my Bey.
Father, with your permission, I can't stay.
-I'll go and take Holofira.
-I don't allow it, Orhan.
-You will not go.
-Father.
Orhan.
If you try to go now,
You'll be giving Yakup a
leverage. I won't let you do that.
How can I stay, father?
-Tell me, how can I stay?
-Son.
They just went there to
ask for her hand in marriage.
If she doesn't want it,
her family won't allow it.
And Holofira will not accept.
-Father...
-Orhan.
Otherwise
we will do as Ghazi says.
If Holofira does not accept, of course.
Excuse me, my Bey.
He will kidnap her for sure, my Bey.
Olivia Hatun, we didn't
get a chance to meet before.
It is nice to meet you, Sultan Yakup.
But I am curious about the
reason for your sudden visit.
I hope there's nothing unpleasant.
Where Holofira is, there is
no unpleasantness of any kind.
We like Holofira a lot.
You raised her pretty well.
Praise be!
Holofira is my most precious one.
She's the only memory I have of my sister.
I didn't want to send her to
Frontier Marketplace at first.
But she insisted so
much that I couldn't resist.
I'm glad that she insisted
on it and we got to meet.
Right?
That's right. That's right.
Holofira is as precious to us as she is to you.
I don't like talking in circles.
With the order of Allah
and words of the Prophet (PBUH),
I want Holofira for my son Mehmed.
Mehmed! Mehmed!
You're walking towards your death, Mehmed!
And if I'm Orhan..
...if I'm Orhan, I'll make you pay for this!
Brother, brother. Don't do this.
-What are you doing? Pull yourself together.
-How can I stay?
How can I stay, Alaeddin?
That dastard named Mehmed
went to ask the woman I love to marry him.
-I can't stay, I'll go.
-Brother!
Brother, just calm down.
If I hadn't heard, I wouldn't have known.
How could my mother and
my sister hide it from me?
Just take a breath. Come,
sit down and take a breath.
Listen to me first.
If you go now, you'll
make Holofira even angrier.
You can go to the marketplace
tomorrow and find out the truth.
Also I do not think Holofira
would accept it, brother.
She wouldn't, right? She
wouldn't, right brother?
-Of course she wouldn't.
-She wouldn't.
But I forced her a lot. She
said I won't be a Muslim
-but I pushed her.
-No.
Holofira is a smart girl, she
knows why you're doing it.
Of course she knows it.
She doesn't say it to me.
But I know.
Holofira loves me too. I know it.
I heard about it. Fatma
told me. My father said it too.
Just because they asked for her for marriage...
it doesn't mean it's going to happen.
Let's say they accepted it,
then we will go and kidnap her, brother.
Then we will go and kidnap her.
But it seems like we will
kidnap two women, right?
-Alaeddin.
-Brother.
Thank you. Thank you.
Alaeddin.
Even our destiny was written at the same time.
-We have the same trouble.
-That's right, brother.
-Hey, what about me?
-I resent you.
Your tongue speaks everything one can think of,
but how could you not tell me this, sister?
Brother.
I was afraid of my mother, brother.
Otherwise I swear I would
say it. I can't hurt you.
All right, I forgive you for now.
Alaeddin brother.
Bala mother.
Vasilis knows Yenisehir
like the palm of his hand.
If they close one gate, he knows very
well where another gate will lead us.
Knowing the gates is not
enough to win a battle, Gera.
No, no. You don't get it, Mongol.
Think about the ambush we set against Yakup.
Think about how the Beys there
were worried and lost their faith.
They all rely on Osman only.
The hearts of all Muslims
are beating in Yenisehir.
are beating in Yenisehir,
and we are keeping that heart in our hands.
Osman will attack our
castles like a hungry wolf.
When he set out on his
first military expedition
Yenisehir will be left to us.
Yenisehir, his family and his precious people,
he will lose everything he has.
I liked your plan, Crusader.
Spend the night here, we will
talk about everything. Everything.
Very well, I liked your plan too, Mongol.
I don't believe her, mother.
I got my answer from her eyes that day.
But today she was someone else, not Gonca.
Maybe there's something she is afraid of.
Yes. There's something she's
afraid of that we do not now, mother.
-But I'll find it out.
-You will.
My brave boy grew up
and fell in love, is that so?
Look at you.
-What are you talking as mother and son?
-It's not something important, my Bey.
It isn't important, is that so?
Alaeddin.
You're secretive, are you
secretive to your father as well?
Astagfirullah, father.
I'll tell you about it, but I'll say it
when the time comes, my Bey.
Okay. so, has Orhan calmed down?
He's all right, he's better.
With your permission, father.
You have it.
Well, Bala Hatun... Tell me.
-Who does Alaaddin love?
-Think about it.
Say it, father Osman.
-I can see it in my son's eyes.
-Well?
Alaaddin loves Gonca.
Oh... Look at Osman Bey.
State affairs and sons are different things.
But we should think carefully.
Alaaddin told Gonca he loves her.
But Gonca said she doesn't lover him back.
Alright then.
Look into Gonca's eyes tomorrow.
You will find the answer there
and we will act accordingly.
Don't worry.
Never!
That's impossible.
You shouldn't cut it off so fast, Olivia Hatun.
-You think first.
-I said it's impossible, Yakup Bey.
We heard that you were
having troubles with the trade.
If we become relatives, we'd
like to get rid of those troubles.
Trade, gold...
They don't matter to me, Saadet Hatun.
Holofira is a Christian.
You are Muslims.
And I will never let Holofira become a Muslim.
We don't have such an
intention. Whatever Holofira wants.
You say this today.
How can I know you won't change your
mind when they get married tomorrow?
This is not a matter of now, Olivia Hatun.
We won't force anyone to be a Muslim.
That's not a tiny matter that should
be left to tomorrow, Yakup Bey.
As long as I live, Holofira
can't become a Muslim.
She can't and she won't.
-Right, Holofira?
-Yes.
I don't intend to become a Muslim.
Today or tomorrow...
We have no intention to make Holofira Muslim.
There are lots of Christians among our people.
You can inquire about it. We
didn't force anyone to be a Muslim.
Now give us an answer.
This is an important matter.
I will think about it, Yakup Bey.
We'll be expecting good news from you.
We should go now.
Alps, are the preparations done?
Thank Allah. Everything is set, my Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
Ayhan Agha... Dastard!
He infiltrated among us.
He caressed our beard
and put the knife on our head.
People don't know who to trust anymore.
They couldn't build fear in
our hearts but people are afraid.
They attack from the shadows. So will we.
We won't stop. Even if Ayhan
Agha goes, Vasilis will come instead.
Even if he goes, someone will definitely come.
They stay there. And we will always stay here.
There will be no peace for us, huh, my Bey?
Those who fight for Allah...
...should leave their peace first.
But we will never stop working
to make people have peace again.
We will eradicate the cruel..
...so that they won't
attempt to attack us again.
We can do this only
with war and conquests.
Praise be!
Exactly!
Alps! For this reason, continue
the preparations in the headquarters!
As you ordered, we're both
continuing the preparations...
...and letting everyone know about it.
The dog must have already heard about it.
All the preparations are also
done in Yenisehir, my Bey.
Okay. Everybody get
back to their duties now.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
If there is confusion in your
mind, don't come to the fight.
If there is a battle, don't
hold me back, my Bey.
The matter is in my heart, not my mind.
And there is nothing to prevent
my desire to fight, for sure.
Thank you, thank you.
Come on! Come on!
Germiyanoglu border - Frontier Market
I sent you to Yenisehir...
...to inform me about
Osman's every plan, Cerkutay.
Why didn't you let me know
about Osman's raid on the caravan?
My Sultan, they don’t trust me
or let me go among them yet.
They will.
You have to gain their
trust in no time, Cerkutay.
Have you got doubts? Ha?
Did your being in Yenisehir
relieve the fury inside you?
They kept you away from
your son for so many years.
For years,
...you were a prisoner.
Nobody looked for you.
Did you forget that?
I didn't.
They left you alone. And I set you free.
I don't want pay back, Cerkutay.
I expect you to serve your country and nation.
I will more than my best..
...until the last drop of my blood, my Sultan.
Now go to Yenisehir.
I'll be expecting news from you.
With your permission.
Cerkutay.
Although they don't trust you, I do.
Know this.
If you'll allow me.
Mother.
You called me?
Do you have anything to say to me, Gonca?
No, I don't.
How many times. How many times you were..
Lying to my face.
I gave you a duty.
To have Alaeddin fall for
you. And what did you do?
You rejected the man who
confessed his love for you!
Why? While everything was going as we wanted.
Why did you do that, Gonca?
How do you know of this?
Mother, are you having me watched? To who?
You wanted this. You lied to me, Gonca!
Then, how do you know I lied mother!
I know.
You fell for Alaeddin.
-Gonca why?
-Enough!
Enough!
Enough mother, enough! You do not know!
None of you knows!
You do not understand me.
You left me no choice, Gonca.
From now on, whatever I say goes.
Inform Master Gera immediately.
Osman. Osman crossed the line mongol!
He thinks he is unbeatable!
He thinks he is unbeatable as we fall back!
The thing he doesn't know is, he will lose
Yenisehir without seeing Kite's borders.
I will burn his Yenisehir down!
Destroying Yenisehir is not enough.
While you are destroying Yenisehir..
I will attack Osman's
encampment and have his head.
Good.
Ayci.
Tell soldiers to prepare. We will
strike Osman's Kite encampment.
Alright. We will make a
heaven from the hell we'll cause.
-We will do it together, Mongol.
-Gera...
Osman is a cautious man. Do not forget.
Or you will be that hell fire.
We will place the flying fires
everywhere around Yenisehir.
Ayhan Aga is dead.
Today, they will meet Master Gera!
Osman and his alps has left the city.
Alright.
The time has come. We are starting.
Did they give Holofira away?
Fatma, my angel daughter.
From now on, you are forbidden to talk.
What am I to do, mother?
I accidentally said it..
After seeing my brother like that.
Watch what you say.
-Bala. Did you talk with Alaeddin?
-Yes?
Fatma heard it right. Gonca
told him that she doesn't love him.
However, Alaeddin says he doesn't believe it.
It seems she is scared of her father.
She doesn't look like she gets scared.
She does not. There is something, however..
We will learn.
How easy it was to look after
the children when they are small.
We thought it would get easier after they
grow up, however it is different every day.
This is the last slope I hope.
We will be relieved, after having them wed.
If Allah permits.
However, how will we give this one away?
No. I won't give her to anyone.
My talkative daughter will
get grow up with me here.
Sure. I can stay with you.
Gonca Hatun. Let me go and talk with her.
You stay here Fatma. I'll go.
My daughter what did I tell you?
-Mother.
-Help me, come on.
-I'm hungry.
-Move.
-Gonca.
-Bala Hatun?
My daughter. Come, let us talk.
Alaeddin told me some things.
I wanted to hear from you as well.
That matter is closed, Bala Hatun.
-There is no need to talk. If you'll allow me..
-Gonca.
I know what love is.
I know a woman who looks with love as well.
I see that love in both of you.
Your mouth denies it, however..
No, Bala Hatun.
That can not happen.
If the matters between the
grown-ups is what you are scared of..
Those are bound to get resolved.
You tell me what you want. I will find a way.
I do not love Alaeddin Bey.
What did she say? She said no, right?
Ulgen. Now you tell me.
What is going on behind this. Tell
me what do you know about Gonca.
I do not know. I do not know anything.
Ulgen, tell me. I am listening.
They are going to the passages.
They are heading to the
passages. Hold the exits, quickly!
Alps, this way.
This street is never this
empty, Vasilis. Be cautious.
We were looking for you.
Osman Bey... You found me.
You think you are a hunter
when you are cornered like a prey.
But blood made you blind.
And since you see red...
..you cannot see who is stronger than you.
I can see, Osman. It is
your turn to see now, Osman.
I placed flying flames in every
corner of your beautiful city.
You will see how this beautiful city
of yours burn and turn into ashes.
We caught all of your men.
Now it is your turn.
But first, you will answer.
You will tell us everything in detail.
I will tell you everything
I know with pleasure.
But this will not stop what is going to happen.
You and your Muslim people will...
...get out of these lands.
These lands were watered
with our martyrs' blood.
Then it was turned into an Islamic land.
We will not bow down to the cruel,
and we will not give you a piece of land.
Osman! I actually admire you.
You've made progress so
far. But it's the end of the road.
These lands are mine! My lands!
You will give me what is mine, Osman!
-Come at me now.
-Attack!
Do not die before you kill them!
The war is just beginning, Osman.
The war is just beginning.
We will not step back!
I will kill you all one by
one today. But first, you!
You always attacked us like a
shadow. Now come at me like a man!
We never let the cruel win!
Orhan! Go to the frontiers marketplace!
Provide security there, my
son. I will bring this dog there.
Yes my Bey.
Take this! Come on!
-What are we waiting for, Commander?
-Wait.
-Trap...
-Trap, right.
You will hit me with my own weapon, huh, Osman?
Dirty man..
He is protecting his headquarters
with traps, he knew we would come.
He must've known about Gera as well,
since he knew about us.
The Crusader was lured into a trap.
What are we going to do, Commander?
We will attack him from his weakest spot.
We are leaving. Come on, my soldiers.
-What did you think would happen, huh?
-Osman...
I was just starting to like you.
Vasilis! Thomas! Run!
-Master!
-Run away!
-You will come back for revenge.
You will make the Crusade stronger.
Stand up! Stand up!
My Bey. This dog's cubs ran away my Bey.
We have the head of the snake.
Let its tail run away. Let it run away.
Come on. Bring him. We are
going to the frontiers marketplace.
-Come on!
-Come on! Walk!
Come on! Walk!
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Holofira did not come.
Look... You are curious about her.
How are we going to learn
what she said, mother?
My daughter... Didn't you hear your brother?
She did not accept becoming a Muslim.
Do not talk about this subject again.
What happened, Malhun Hatun?
Why are you looking at Holofira's counter?
What happened Saadet Hatun?
Were you watching us?
No... I was looking at
my bride-to-be's counter...
And I saw you.
Did Holofira accept getting married?
Right. Holofira is now my daughter-in-law.
I don't want to see Orhan at my marketplace.
Keep your son away.
Who are you to decide
where my son goes or leaves?
Malhun... I am the owner
of this frontiers marketplace.
And I am Holofira’s mother-in-law.
What? Whose mother-in-law are you?
What are you saying, Saadet Hatun?
You heard it, Orhan Bey.
Holofira is my daughter-in-law now.
I don't want to see you around her now.
Orhan!
-Orhan?
-You... you...
How could you do this to me Holofira?
Orhan.. What happened? I don't understand.
I could never know you
would do this, Lord's daughter.
Never.
They moved away from our arrow, but...
...my brother's revenge will be taken!
Get ready to burn and destroy!
My soldiers! We came and we saw!
Now it is time to destroy them!
You will be settled in every corner of the
market. Everyone will keep their eyes open.
We will see what the
situation is in the marketplace.
Yes my Shahzade.
The great people of my lands, welcome.
Yakup.
Yakup...
This doesn't suit you, Yakup Bey.
How could you do this.
You did such a terrible thing
just to take me behind you, Yakup?
It doesn't suit you, Yakup Bey.
What you did doesn't suit you at all.
Maybe he did what suits him, right?
Enough!
You forced me into it.
I said I don't like confusion.
I said if someone's mind is confused,
he shouldn't keep his mind over his body.
You didn't get it.
We didn't take these lands just to lose them
because of someone's dreams.
I will not let you
ruin these lands because of that dreams.
You will walk in my path.
I'll give you Alps.
I'll give you power.
Under my command,
we will conquer both east and west.
Osman Bey is coming.
Did you invite Osman Bey too?
I called someone else,
but he is coming before us. Come, Osman.
Selamun Aleykum.
-What is he doing here?
-We'll find it out, Hatun.
We will find it out.
Yakup Sultan. Once again,
we did what you needed to do.
You have only fallen into a trap.
What nonsense are you talking about, Osman Bey?
If you have something
to say, say it. If not, leave.
I have something to tell you.
I also have things to say to people.
Alps. Bring him.
Who is he?
One of the heads of the snake.
One of those who trapped you
and tricked you. Yakup Bey.
One of those who sat
in our table and killed us.
You know him as merchant Ayhan Agha.
His real name is Gera. One
of the leaders of Crusaders.
You dastard!
Did you have other dreams?
The dream is not mine, Osman.
It is the dream of those who believe in Jesus.
You will all die.
You will all die and be buried
under these sacred lands.
You will all die, Osman.
Look.
Look at me.
We will always prevail as you
keep saying "you will be destroyed."
Come here. Look at me.
We will always stand upright
as long as you try to ruin us.
Get up! Get up!
You oppress your own people, as if it's
not enough, you oppress my people too.
Look at me. I'm the one who
destroys the cruel ones, Gera.
You might fool other people with what you say
but you can't fool me.
You will be ruined.
Look at me. Look at me.
Lift your head.
These innocent people you see will be
the ones who will take revenge on infidels.
Haven't you heard about it?
They say "be afraid of the
anger of innocent ones."
Nobody told you about this?
They did, Osman.
Let your people
hear the last words of the
man who will lose his head.
Your Osman Bey wants to establish a state
that will stand tall as himself.
He will never be able to establish
that state, if you follow him,
you will all die. Even without us, Mongols,
Mongols will kill you
all. These lands are ours!
These lands are ours, Osman!
We will resist against the oppressors
and we will always prevail
under the banner of Islam.
We will prevail even if there
are those who are afraid.
We will rise even if there
are those who run away.
With the permission of
Allah we will always prevail.
-Allah is the greatest
Visit turkision.com for more!